On the agenda, be passed.
反對嘅請舉手。
同埋動議議案，石禮謙議員。
我現在向各位提出嘅代議議題係石禮謙議員動議嘅議案，予以通過。有冇議員想發言？
委員會 held a meeting with the administration on 13 November 2018 to examine the subsidiary legislation.
如果冇，我再向各位提出上述嘅代決議題。石禮謙議員動議嘅議案予以通過，贊成嘅請舉手。
Legislation to 9102019. With these remarks, Madam President, I urge members to support the motion.
At the House Committee meeting held on 2 November 2008, members decided to form a subcommittee to scrutinise the subsidiary legislation.
我認為議題獲得功能團體選舉及分區直選產生兩部分在席議員分別以過半數贊成，我宣佈議案獲得通過。第五項議案延展於二零一八年十月三十一號提交本會省覽嘅二零一八年。
部分在席議員分別以過半數贊成，我宣佈議案獲得通過。第四項議案延展於二零一八年十月三十一號提交本會省覽嘅二零一八年土地雜項條文修訂規例嘅修訂期限，我邀請石禮謙議員發言。
Thank you, Madam President. In my capacity as chairman of the subcommittee on land, excuse me, in my capacity as chairman of the subcommittee on land miscellaneous provisions amendment regulation 2018, I move the motion under my name as printed.
to allow sufficient time for the subcommittee to consider the supplementary information provided by the administration pursuant to members' requests made at the meeting and report its deliberations to the House committee. I call upon members to support the motion on extending the period for scrutinising the subsidiary.